[Riley] Previously on The Chi...
[Kiesha] I'm really excited
I'm finally marrying Emmett.
[Riley] Hey. Shaad. can we
talk to you for a minute?
I want to give you the house
I bought for me and Jada.
-That means a lot to me.
-Appreciate y'all.
[Victor] I did it.
You want me to arrest you
for Nuck's murder?
Yes.
[Fatima]
I know you didn't do this.
[Victor] She's got kids.
-You got me.
-Do I?
I got myself in some shit
I can't get out of.
I just feel like the hole
is getting deeper and deeper.
[Britney] This is why you
should move to Atlanta with me.
You gonna let my brother go.
-You killed Nuck?
-[Reg] Yeah.
Reginald Taylor.
you're under arrest
for the murder of Nicasio Sosa.
[Rafi] Don't make me
knock your ass out.
Do it.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
♪♪♪
[Kiesha] I'm grateful
to have someone in my life
I know I can trust.
[Emmett]
I have to tell you something.
-Tiff killed Nuck.
-What?
She found out
that Nuck killed Rob.
and she took him out.
I can't believe you killed
the father of my child.
He killed mine first.
I don't even want you
at the wedding.
To be honest.
I don't want you in my life.
♪ Solemn music ♪
♪♪♪
♪ solemn jazz music ♪
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
[Emmett sighs]
I disinvited Tiff
to the wedding.
♪♪♪
We can't cut her
out of our lives.
Yes. we can.
I know what she did
was fucked up.
But she's still
the mother of my child.
She killed the father of mine.
[sighs]
He killed the father of hers.
Whose side are you on?
I'm just trying to do
what's best for us.
And whether we like it or not.
she always gonna be our family.
I can't have my wedding
at her house.
We get married
in less than 24 hours.
-We need a location.
-Let's just have it here.
We can't fit
all those people in here.
♪♪♪
[Kiesha sighs]
I know where we can do it.
Where?
Let me surprise you.
I can't take no more surprises.
Do you trust me?
♪♪♪
Do you?
Yeah.
Let me take care of this.
♪ Mellow music ♪
♪♪♪
[Victor]
I just wanted to protect Tiff.
I'm glad you did.
♪♪♪
You think Tiff and Kiesha
gonna survive this?
[sighs] I don't know.
-Hey.
-[Victor] Hey. hey.
The man of the hour.
What's up. boy?
Congrats on the new house.
Hey. I'm just grateful to
Darnell for letting us have it.
That's gonna be
our forever home.
And Kiesha gonna be
my forever girl.
I'm really happy for y'all. man.
Yeah. it took us long enough.
but we finally here.
[Shaad] Finally.
Love is a battlefield.
Hey. man. we all just trying
to survive.
-I'm barely making it.
-Hey.
We've all come a long way.
Uh. that's why. uh...
I want y'all to be my groomsmen.
Damn. nigga.
you just now asking us?
Hey. it's been
a crazy few weeks. but...
-Oh. we got you.
-Let's go.
-Yeah. yeah.
-Whatever you need.
-[Victor chuckles]
-Great. 'cause. uh...
I'm gonna need
to borrow your new backyard.
♪♪♪
Hey.
♪ Dramatic jazz music ♪
♪♪♪
[Tiff] I'm sorry.
That's not gonna cut it.
I know.
I can't believe
you took someone's life.
I couldn't let him live
after what he did.
What about Ronnie?
Now he has to grow up
without a father.
Him and Junior
have that in common.
[sighs]
I'm sorry he did that to you.
Me too.
I don't know
if I can forgive you.
But I will...
♪ soft music ♪
for our children's sake.
Thank you.
It'll take time.
Take all the time you need.
♪♪♪
[sighs]
[Victor] I'm staying
out of trouble from now on.
I've heard this before.
I mean it this time.
♪ Got the drip.
I'm ready to go ♪
I hope so.
♪ R&B music playing ♪
Will you be my date to Emmett
and Kiesha's wedding?
I already have one.
♪ All I really need to know ♪
Who?
Isis.
She broke up with her man.
so she's ready
to find somebody new.
and she thinks weddings are
a great place to meet people.
Mm.
So you trying to meet somebody?
♪♪♪
♪ So. baby. take your time ♪
I already got my eye on someone.
♪ What's the rush.
what's the rush ♪
♪ What's the rush ♪
I'll see you there?
I look forward to it.
♪ There'll be lows and highs
that we got to get over ♪
♪ Everything's gonna be
all right ♪
♪ Everything's
gonna be all right ♪
♪ We got love ♪
♪ I keep these thoughts
incarcerated in my mind ♪
♪ Locked behind a wall
of indoctrination... ♪
[Bakari sighs]
♪ Confidence and cockiness
to compensate ♪
♪ For the misogyny
of pick-up lines ♪
♪ My hips are wide. inherited
from my Grandma Ellen's side ♪
♪ Sometimes I think I got
pieces of her depression ♪
♪ My lyric expression like
New York delicatessens... ♪
-I'm ready to leave.
-For real?
Yeah. me and Lynae want to come
to Atlanta with you.
[chuckles] Let's go.
♪♪♪
-[Bakari] Hmm.
-[Britney sighs]
I love you. sis.
I love you too.
♪♪♪
Whee!
♪ Upbeat jazz music ♪
[Darnell]
Where'd you get the idea
to have the wedding here. son?
Ma.
She finally came
to me in a dream.
♪ Soft music ♪
Hmm. This... this was her idea?
♪♪♪
We were right there
in y'all's garden
when she was talking to me.
She was surrounded by flowers.
[breathes deeply]
She looked so beautiful.
♪♪♪
When we realized we couldn't
do it at Tiff's anymore. uh...
the only other place
I could think of was here.
♪♪♪
[sniffles] You ready?
Been ready.
[Darnell] You're not nervous?
No.
I know I'm doing
the right thing.
[chuckles] Yeah.
All right.
Then let's get you married. son.
[laughter]
-[Emmett] Love you.
-[Darnell] I love you too.
♪ Vedo's "Take It There"
playing ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Sometimes we take
this love for granted ♪
♪ And how precious life can be ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ But every time
I think about her touch ♪
♪ Every time I. every time
I talk about her love ♪
♪ I get choked up ♪
♪ This is real love ♪
♪ So I might take it there ♪
♪ We might take it there ♪
♪ 'Cause it's been on my mind ♪
♪ So let's not waste no time ♪
♪ 'Cause I might take it there ♪
♪ We might take it there ♪
♪ 'Cause it's been on my mind ♪
♪ Might be the perfect time ♪
♪ For me to take it there ♪
♪ Do the right thing by you ♪
♪ The first time is
my only time ♪
♪ Gotta be sure about you ♪
♪ Pray the Lord
to give me a sign ♪
♪ I know she's the right one ♪
♪ No one like her ♪
♪ I can tell
she was made for me ♪
♪ And it didn't take long
for me to see but ♪
♪ Sometimes we take
this love for granted ♪
♪ And how precious
life could be ♪
♪ But every time
I think about her touch ♪
♪ Every time I. every time
I think about her love ♪
♪ I get choked up ♪
♪ This is real love ♪
♪ So I might take it there ♪
♪ We might take it there ♪
♪ 'Cause it's been on my mind ♪
♪ So let's not waste no time ♪
♪ 'Cause I might take it there ♪
♪ We might take it there ♪
♪ 'Cause it's been on my mind ♪
♪ Might be the perfect time ♪
♪ So I might take it there ♪
♪ We might take it there ♪
♪ 'Cause it's been on my mind ♪
♪ So let's not waste no time ♪
♪ 'Cause I might take it there ♪
♪ We might take it there ♪
♪ 'Cause it's been on my mind ♪
♪ Might be the perfect time ♪
♪ So I might take it there ♪
♪ We might take it there ♪
♪ 'Cause it's been on my mind ♪
♪ So let's not waste no time ♪
♪ 'Cause I might take it there ♪
♪ We might take it there ♪
♪ If you're ready. baby ♪
♪ 'Cause it's been on my mind ♪
♪ Might be the perfect time ♪
I can't believe this day has...
[chuckles]
-Has finally come.
-[laughs]
You look beautiful.
Thank you for stepping in.
I always wanted a daughter.
[sighing] How do you feel?
Like...
I'm about to marry
my best friend.
[both laughing]
That's a beautiful feeling.
I hope today
doesn't make you sad.
Why would it?
It might remind you of...
the husband you lost.
Weddings remind me
of the love we shared.
And that'll never make me sad.
♪ Soft music ♪
♪♪♪
Surprise.
Ma. Ma.
♪♪♪
[crying softly]
You came back.
I wouldn't miss this
for the world.
You missed the birth
of my second child.
♪♪♪
I'll probably be apologizing
for that one
for the rest of my life.
You were here for the first.
so I'll forgive you.
[chuckles]
♪♪♪
[both laughing]
Hey. Shaad. it's five o'clock
somewhere. man.
[Shaad] It most certainly is.
Pass that glass. bro.
[Victor] Y'all playing around.
Kiesha gonna get on that ass
y'all get some on them suits.
So...
I need you to hold on
to this for me.
♪ You remember.
from the beginning ♪
♪ You were right there
with me. right there... ♪
-What if I lose it?
-You won't.
How do you know?
Because...
I believe in you.
♪ Always right there with me ♪
♪ Always right there ♪
♪ Right there with me ♪
♪ Right there all along ♪
♪ You know the secrets
that nobody... ♪
I won't let you down.
Better not.
♪ Soft music ♪
I love you. Dad.
I love you too.
♪♪♪
[breathes deeply]
♪ Mellow music ♪
♪♪♪
When did you get out?
You not happy to see me?
Of course I am.
I just didn't know
you were gonna be here.
[chuckles] Yeah.
I was trying to surprise you.
Well. consider me surprised.
♪♪♪
Right.
I heard Nuck is dead.
A lot of shit has happened
since you've been gone.
♪♪♪
Well. I'm back now.
OK.
♪♪♪
I know that look.
What look?
You got a new nigga. don't you?
I didn't want to be alone
forever.
I understand.
♪♪♪
I'm sorry.
Me too.
♪♪♪
You going to Emmett
and Kiesha's wedding?
-Yeah.
-Let's go together.
-OK.
-[chuckles]
Maybe this can be our. uh...
our last dance.
[chuckles] I'd like that.
♪ R&B music ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪♪♪
♪ We got some real music
going. some real... ♪
Mm.
Whew.
[sighs]
I know Emmett's getting married.
but I wanted to say
congrats to you too.
Thank you. brother.
You're a proud homeowner now.
[chuckles]
I never thought I'd see the day.
Me either.
♪♪♪
We been through a lot. man.
I know.
Some shit I wish
we could take back.
[scoffs] Who you telling?
[sighs]
You always been
like a brother to me.
♪♪♪
I don't know if I would've
made it without you.
♪♪♪
I'll never forget you.
Well. damn. nigga.
I ain't dying.
[both chuckling]
Life has dealt us
some bad hands.
Mm.
But I'm glad we stuck together
through it all.
♪ Indistinct singing ♪
♪♪♪
You're my brother for life.
I love you. man.
I love you too.
♪ We know ♪
♪ Yeah. we know ♪
♪♪♪
[bell jingling]
-[Keith] Yo. man. we're closed.
-[Rafi] I know.
I'm looking for somebody.
[Keith] Who?
Bakari.
♪ Ominous music ♪
What you want with him?
We got some unfinished business.
♪♪♪
I don't know where he at.
♪ R&B music ♪
♪♪♪
You want some champagne?
I'm sober now.
Since when?
This morning. [chuckles]
And what brought about
this life change?
I need to stop leaning
on external things
to make me feel better.
Me too.
And I know my father
would expect more from me.
I'm proud of you.
♪♪♪
I want to get back
to my old self.
I've missed the old Papa.
Me too.
I'm glad I met you.
I'm glad you came back.
And I'll never leave
your side again.
You promise?
♪♪♪
As long as you give me
a reason to stay.
I'll always be here.
I got you.
♪ I'm reaching for the stars ♪
♪ Oh. you know it ♪
Weddings always make me
emotional.
Mm. me too.
Zuri. you want to be next?
Uh. not yet. [laughs]
-You scared?
-A little.
Marriage is a big commitment.
Yeah. that's a different
kind of faithful.
It does feel like
a lot of pressure.
But we can handle that.
I don't know if y'all could.
When you trying to tie the knot?
[chuckles] I got to find
the right woman first.
-I could hook you up.
-Oh. no.
Last time you hooked me up
with somebody.
I had to file
for a restraining order.
That wasn't my fault.
So what you looking for
in a lady?
I like them tall
with a big personality.
Ah. you date white girls?
Only if they're Jewish.
[chuckles] You're crazy.
I'm ready to settle down.
I don't want to be
a lone soldier forever.
Well. you'll meet
that special someone
when you least expect it.
I keep telling God I'm ready.
Well. God does answer prayers.
-Mm-hmm. Yes. He does.
-[Zuri giggles]
♪♪♪
Why you looking at apartments?
My building going up
on the rent.
♪♪♪
You want to move in with me?
-Don't play with me.
-I'm not.
That's a big step.
I know.
Are you ready for that?
I think so.
You better be sure.
Let's just try.
[Desiree clicks tongue]
Does that make us official?
What you mean by "official"?
I mean no cheating.
Mm...
sure.
You don't sound sure. [chuckles]
I can't promise I'll be perfect.
but I'm down to try.
♪♪♪
[sighs] Me too.
♪ Stevie Wonder's "You and I" ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Here we are ♪
♪ On Earth together ♪
♪ It's you and I ♪
♪ God has made us ♪
♪ Fall in love ♪
♪ It's true ♪
♪ I've really found ♪
♪ Someone like you ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Will it stay ♪
♪ The love you feel for me ♪
♪ Will it say ♪
♪ That you will be by my side ♪
♪ To see me through ♪
♪ Until my life ♪
♪ Is through ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Well. in my mind ♪
♪ We can conquer the world ♪
♪♪♪
♪ In love. you and I ♪
♪ You and I ♪
♪♪♪
[Charles] Everyone please stand
for the bride.
♪ I am glad ♪
♪ At least in my life ♪
♪ I found someone ♪
♪ That may not be here forever ♪
♪ To see me through ♪
♪ But I found strength ♪
♪ In you ♪
-What's your name. girl?
-Kiesha.
[Emmett] You're a blessing.
you know that?
♪ I only pray... ♪
[Emmett] I'm proud of you. girl.
[Kiesha] I'm proud of me too.
♪ That I have shown you... ♪
[Kiesha] I could look at you
for hours and hours.
[Emmett] I could look at you
for the rest of my life.
♪ Because that's all ♪
♪ That I am living for ♪
[Emmett] Kiesha.
you're an angel on this Earth.
♪ Don't worry... ♪
[Emmett] I don't know
what I'd do without you.
[Kiesha] Emmett. I always knew
we would end up here.
I want to hold your hand...
until the end of time.
♪♪♪
♪ You will stay here ♪
♪ Always ♪
♪ And. love ♪
♪ You and I ♪
♪ You and I... ♪
Ready?
♪ You and I ♪
♪ You and. oh ♪
♪ In my mind ♪
♪ We can conquer ♪
♪ The world ♪
♪♪♪
♪ In love. you and I ♪
You look beautiful.
Thank you.
♪ You and I ♪
♪♪♪
[Charles] Dearly beloved.
we are gathered here today
to join this man...
and this woman
in holy matrimony.
It's been a long time coming.
[Kiesha chuckles]
But the day has finally come
to say "I do."
We are all honored to witness
two beautiful souls become one.
Kiesha...
it took me a while
to write my vows.
probably 'cause
it took me a while
to become the man I am today.
All I know is...
I don't know who I'd be
without you.
You made me want to be
a better version of myself.
You inspire me.
You uplift me.
You showed up for me
when I was in a hospital bed...
and you didn't know if I was
going to make it out alive.
[inhales deeply]
[voice breaking] You were
a wife before you became one.
[breathes deeply]
It took me some time
to become a husband.
And I'm so grateful
for your patience.
Thank you for being
a phenomenal mother
to our children.
Thank you for being
the heartbeat of our family.
[exhales shakily]
Thank you for being
all that you are.
And thank you
for never giving up on me.
Emmett...
we grew up together.
We seen each other
through a lot.
We weathered...
many storms.
We've lost parents.
And we welcomed the new life
into this world
and became a family.
We were there for each other
through all of it.
Every step has led
to this moment.
And I wouldn't trade any of it
for the world.
Thank you for letting me in.
Thank you for being a partner...
for your willingness
to grow and evolve.
Thank you for never giving up
on this family.
[exhales shakily]
Emmett...
do you take Kiesha to be
your lawfully wedded wife.
to have and to hold
from this day forward
till death do you part?
I do.
Kiesha...
do you take Emmett to be
your lawfully wedded husband.
to have and to hold
from this day forward
till death do you part?
I do.
By the power vested in me.
I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
-You may kiss your bride.
-[cheers and applause]
♪ Everything I do ♪
♪ Everything that I do. girl ♪
♪ Starts with
a little bit of you ♪
♪ Every time. every action... ♪
[Charles] Ladies and gentlemen.
I present to you
Mr. and Mrs. Emmett Washington.
[cheers and applause]
♪♪♪
♪ Everything that I do ♪
♪ Starts with
a little bit of you ♪
♪ Making flavor. kissing ♪
♪ And fragrance
from the kitchen ♪
[cheers and applause]
♪ And I never want
to give it up ♪
♪ Everything I do ♪
♪ Everything that I do. girl ♪
[indistinct chatter]
♪ Mellow music ♪
♪♪♪
-Hey. hey.
-[Victor chuckles]
♪♪♪
-Congratulations.
-Thanks. Tiff.
-Don't fuck it up this time.
-Hey. I won't.
You better not.
I'm sorry.
[Tiff] For what?
For everything
you had to survive.
-It wasn't all your fault.
-But some of it was.
♪♪♪
I just wanted you
to know I'm sorry.
Thank you.
[inhales deeply]
If you ever need anything.
we're here for you.
That means a lot to me.
I love you. Tiff.
I love you too.
♪ That's what they told me ♪
♪ Leave us alone ♪
♪ indistinct singing ♪
Hello.
-Mm-hmm. You're beautiful.
-[glasses clinking]
[Victor clears throat]
[Shaad chuckles]
It's an honor to be
one of your best men.
Y'all know we got to do
everything together. right?
[laughter]
Mushrooms and best-man speeches.
It'd be an understatement
to say that Emmett has
a way with the ladies.
[laughter. cheers]
[Shaad] Yeah. but now
he's officially retired.
I heard that.
That's the thing about love.
It changes you.
We watched you grow
from a boy to a man...
not because you had to
but because you wanted to.
Yeah. if love was that easy.
everybody'd do it.
No wonder some of y'all
still single out there.
[Victor] Easy.
-Easy.
-Yeah. you did.
We just really glad that...
Emmett and Kiesha decided
to rise to the challenge.
[Victor] Hmm.
Every day you have
to choose each other.
[Shaad]
And as long as you do that...
your love will continue
to flourish over the years.
We're proud of the man
you've become. bro.
You've given us all something
we can aspire to.
Kiesha...
[laughter]
You represent
all of the women...
who have ever loved us.
And you remind us
that we're all...
worthy of being loved.
You're a queen...
and we honor you.
And we thank you for always
holding your head up high...
and for... and for showing
our boy Emmett where home is.
We love y'all.
[cheers and applause]
Absolutely.
[Victor chuckles.
Shaad sniffles]
[both] To Emmett and Kiesha.
[cheers and applause]
We love you!
♪ Oh. I need it ♪
♪ I can feel it ♪
♪ Feel it. feel it. feel it ♪
♪♪♪
Mmm.
This mac and cheese is hittin'.
It's my secret recipe.
-You made that?
-Yes. ma'am.
Only bank tellers
call me "ma'am."
What your lovers call you?
Oh. you trying to find out.
♪♪♪
Maybe...
I can cook you dinner sometime.
We'll see.
[cheers and applause]
♪ You're turnin' me on ♪
♪ Oh. you make me go insane.
I swear you're fire ♪
♪ You're like the only one
my heart desires ♪
♪ Hey. you're not around.
but yet you all around me ♪
♪ Damn. girl ♪
♪ You're turnin' me on.
you're turnin' me on ♪
-[Victor sighs]
-[Jake] Just go over there.
♪ You're turnin' me on ♪
I'm giving her space.
Mm. don't give her
too much space.
You might lose her again.
-I just don't want to hurt her.
-Then don't.
[scoffs]
Since when did y'all start
giving me advice?
Look. we know a thing or two
about love.
Y'all don't know shit
I'm moving in with my girl
this summer.
♪♪♪
Oh. shit. [scoffs]
I see you. little bro.
[chuckles]
I know.
It's the end of an era.
Shoot. and one of these days.
I'm gonna propose to Kenya.
Oh. hell. no. I can't have
y'all tying the knot before me.
[laughter]
Then you better go talk
to your girl.
♪ You're not around.
but yet you all around me ♪
♪ Yeah. girl ♪
♪ You're turnin' me on ♪
♪ Turnin' me ♪
♪ Luther Vandross'
"A House Is Not a Home" ♪
♪ A chair is still a chair ♪
♪ Even when there's no one ♪
♪ Sitting there ♪
♪♪♪
♪ But a chair ♪
♪ Is not a house ♪
♪ And a house is not a home ♪
♪ When there's no one there ♪
You're so beautiful.
Thank you. Mr. Washington.
You're welcome. Mrs. Washington.
♪ You can give... ♪
You better stop staring
at me like that
before I send
everybody home early.
No. you're not.
I waited too long for this day.
Was it everything
you dreamed of?
It was better.
I'm grateful
I get to do life with you.
I wouldn't want to do life
with anyone else.
♪ Are you gonna be... ♪
Hmm.
Want to make a baby tonight?
-No. I don't.
-[both laughing]
♪♪♪
Yeah. you're right.
We got enough kids.
♪♪♪
I love you.
I love you too.
♪ Me ♪
♪ Yeah. with me ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Still in love ♪
♪ With me ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Kory Leigh's "Your Jam" ♪
♪ Uh-huh ♪
♪♪♪
♪ It's your jam. it's your jam ♪
♪ Turn it up. we gonna dance ♪
♪ It's a vibe. we gonna fly ♪
♪ We in outer space tonight ♪
♪ It's your jam. it's your jam ♪
♪ Turn it up. we gonna dance ♪
♪ It's a vibe. we gonna fly ♪
♪ We in outer space tonight ♪
♪ It's going up... ♪
Nice to see you smiling again.
It's nice to have a reason to.
You gonna be all right in
that big house all by yourself?
[sighs]
Actually. I was wondering
if you and EJ wanted
to move in with me.
You sure?
♪♪♪
Yeah.
I want my family back.
[chuckles] You know we gonna get
on each other's nerves. right?
[sighs] Yeah. I know.
But I think we need each other.
Me too.
♪ It's a vibe. we gonna fly ♪
♪ We in outer space tonight ♪
♪ It's your jam ♪
♪ hip-hop music ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Hold up -♪ Say what ♪
♪ Hold up -♪ What's that ♪
♪ There's a few things
I want to discuss ♪
♪ Allow me to touch
on relationships ♪
♪ When you come across
a good one ♪
♪ Don't burn that bridge. no ♪
♪ 'Cause you never know
when you need it ♪
♪ You can fall on hard times ♪
♪ 'Cause life can go that way ♪
♪ If you don't plan.
you fail. simple and plain ♪
♪ Aha. ah. ah. ah. ah ♪
♪ These are just my views only ♪
♪ Got nothing to do
with you. homey ♪
♪ These are just
my views only. yeah ♪
Can we try this again?
-It depends.
-[chuckles] On what?
On whether or not
we can stick it out.
You left me.
-You're right.
-[laughs]
♪ Go ahead and spin it ♪
-♪ Can I get that.
-♪ Yes. indeed ♪
But I will never
leave you again.
♪ Let me speak.
please don't get... ♪
And I'll never leave you either.
♪ These are just my views
that I'm spewin' ♪
♪ I'm groovin' ♪
You ready to really
commit this time?
I am.
I want to love you forever.
It's a long time.
Not long enough.
♪ Ha ha. yeah. unh ♪
♪ It's so insane ♪
♪ They keep on playing
these games ♪
♪ I love how you pop it ♪
♪ I love how it move
when you drop it ♪
♪ You already know
that you got it ♪
♪ Every time you walk
into a room. you stop it ♪
♪ OK. I'ma put the money
on the books ♪
♪ Break a nigga neck.
tryin' to look ♪
♪ Throw it all on me.
I'm shook ♪
♪ I know what to do with it.
never been a rook ♪
♪ Do a trick. baby.
you know I'm a trip. baby ♪
♪ Type nigga I might make
you rich. baby ♪
♪ I don't really be
in the mix. baby ♪
I heard you moving up
out of here.
Yeah. I'm off to the A tomorrow.
-You deserve a new beginning.
-[scoffs] We all do.
You trying to leave too?
No. but moving in with my girl
kind of feels
like a different life.
[Bakari] It is.
Mm. I'm proud of us.
Me too.
Hey. we're gonna miss you. man.
I'm gonna miss y'all too.
Just come back and visit. nigga.
Y'all can also come see me.
I heard they got some
nice churches out there.
-And some fine-ass girls too.
-See. you already slippin'.
I still got eyes. bro.
♪ It's like we got
a spiritual connection ♪
♪ I ain't even got to say it ♪
♪ 'Cause you're right there
with me ♪
♪ That's the kind of shit
to make your head spin ♪
♪ Oh. oh ♪
♪ It's about time ♪
[cheering]
♪ I finally found
somebody like you ♪
♪ It's about time ♪
♪ I finally found
somebody like you ♪
♪ We got the kind of lovin'
that this can be ♪
♪ And you recognize the real
inside of me ♪
♪ If I didn't have you.
don't know where I'd be ♪
♪ Where would I ♪
♪ Talk to me. boy ♪
♪ Tell me. are you single ♪
♪ Are you free ♪
[crowd cheering]
♪ Wanna know
if you're available ♪
♪ To come and spend some time ♪
♪ And chill with me ♪
[crowd shouts]
♪ If it's cool. let me know ♪
♪ It's on you. we can do ♪
♪ What we feel ♪
[crowd whooping]
♪ If the energy is right ♪
♪ We can do this thing
all night ♪
♪ What's the deal ♪
♪ I got to know ♪
♪ Boy. I just got to know ♪
♪ How you get down. let me see ♪
♪ What it be like. feel like.
taste like ♪
♪ And if we take it there ♪
♪ Would you show me
how you feel ♪
♪ What it be like. feel like.
taste like ♪
♪ Boy. I just got to know ♪
♪ How you get down. let me see ♪
♪ What it be like. feel like.
taste like ♪
♪ And I don't know what to say ♪
♪ You take my breath.
make me weak ♪
♪ What it be like. feel like.
taste like ♪
[crowd cheering]
[indistinct chatter]
♪ Upbeat music ♪
♪ I got all this juice.
let's get loose ♪
♪ And you're all invited ♪
♪ Oh. yeah. uh-huh ♪
♪ Oh. yeah ♪
♪ We gonna call a truce.
bring the deuce ♪
♪ And you're all invited ♪
♪ Oh. yeah. uh-huh ♪
♪ Oh. yeah ♪
♪ Unh. it's a party
in the front. though ♪
♪ Yeah. I'm in the back
smoking pre-rolls ♪
♪ Unh. lot of smoke.
that's the West Coast ♪
♪ Yeah. backyard.
it's a freak show ♪
♪ Unh. it ain't a party
till you naughty ♪
♪ And we know that ♪
♪ Gettin' litty in the city.
yeah. we on that ♪
♪ I got all the juice.
let's get loose ♪
♪ And you're all invited ♪
♪ Oh. yeah. uh-huh ♪
♪ Oh. yeah ♪
♪ We gonna call a truce.
bring the deuce ♪
♪ And you're all invited ♪
♪ Oh. yeah ♪
♪ Come on ♪
♪ To the left ♪
♪ Take it back now. y'all ♪
♪ One hop this time ♪
♪ Right foot. two stomps ♪
♪ Left foot. two stomps ♪
♪ Slide to the left ♪
♪ Slide to the right ♪
♪ Crisscross ♪
♪ Cha-cha real smooth ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Let's go to work ♪
♪ To the left ♪
♪ Take it back now. y'all ♪
♪ Two hops this time ♪
♪ Right foot. two stomps ♪
♪ Left foot. two stomps ♪
♪ Hands on your knees.
hands on your knees ♪
♪ Get funky with it ♪
♪ Oh. yeah ♪
♪ Come on ♪
♪ Cha-cha now. y'all ♪
[excited chatter]
♪ Turn it out ♪
♪ To the left ♪
♪ Take it back now. y'all ♪
♪ Five hops this time ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Right foot. let's stomp ♪
♪ Left foot. let's stomp ♪
♪ Freeze.
everybody clap your hands ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Come on. y'all ♪
♪ Mista's
"Blackberry Molasses" ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Blackberry molasses ♪
♪ One of the things
that never change ♪
♪ You got to keep pushing on ♪
♪ The sun don't reign
all the time ♪
♪ There's gonna be
some heartache and pain ♪
[Jake] You good?
♪ Woke up Sunday morning... ♪
I'm all right.
♪ Got a little bad news today ♪
Thanks for doing what you did.
♪ They say my life
ain't worth livin' ♪
Sometimes you got to take one
for the team.
♪♪♪
We ain't gonna let you
rot in here.
♪♪♪
I'll be fine.
Will you?
♪♪♪
These niggas know better
than to fuck with me.
[chuckles]
We gonna keep visiting.
♪ Sometimes
I'd rather give up instead ♪
You don't have to.
We want to.
We here if you need us.
♪ Blackberry molasses ♪
♪ It'll never change ♪
I love y'all.
♪ The sun don't reign
all the time ♪
♪ There's gonna be
some heartache... ♪
Love you too. bro.
♪♪♪
♪ Don't tell me
how to live my life ♪
Hey.
I'm gonna be OK.
♪♪♪
[Reg sniffles]
♪ Blackberry molasses ♪
♪ One of the things
that never change ♪
[sniffles. clears throat]
♪ You got to keep pushing on ♪
♪ The sun don't reign
all the time ♪
♪ There's gonna be
some heartache and pain ♪
♪♪♪
[Kiesha] I'm proud of you.
Thanks for always looking out.
Make sure you take care
of my little sis.
I got you.
I'm gonna miss you.
We're gonna miss y'all too.
♪ PJ's "To the Ones" playing ♪
♪♪♪
♪ I'll probably go to church
in the morning ♪
♪ I'll probably
throw your name up ♪
♪ I know why he ain't save us ♪
♪ Here's to the ones
that got away ♪
[laughter. chatter]
♪ If I had it all ♪
♪ You're who
I'd trade it all for ♪
♪ And part of it's my fault ♪
♪ It's still some things
I fall for ♪
Welcome to the world. Ronnie.
♪ I had to make a title change ♪
[Kiesha] I love y'all.
-[Nina] Oh. we love you too.
-[laughter]
[person] This is a nice place.
[Kiesha] Thank you.
We just moved in.
♪ To all the ways
it could've played ♪
♪ And to the hearts
they couldn't break ♪
♪ The mistakes
that we didn't make ♪
♪ Here's to the ones
that got away ♪
[Nina] I'm mad you ate
the cheese puffs.
[Kiesha] Oh. my bad.
Come on. baby. we out.
[Nina] What are you doing?
[Kiesha]
Looking at my baby book.
[Nina] Wow.
♪ Here's to the ones
that got away ♪
♪ If I had it all ♪
Thank you. Lord.
for this precious food
our bodies are about to receive.
We want to bless
the hands that made it.
♪ Part of it's my fault ♪
And we ask that You bless
those who don't have food
to put in their bodies.
-You love me. right?
-[Nina] Always.
[Kiesha]
And you love that little boy.
[Nina] Of course.
[Kiesha]
Then that's all that matters.
♪ And I'm moving
out the crying stage ♪
♪ To all the ways
it could've played ♪
♪ And to the hearts
they couldn't break ♪
♪ The mistakes
that we didn't make ♪
♪ Here's to the ones
that got away ♪
♪ Here's to
the ones that got away ♪
♪ Here's to the ones
that got away ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Away. ooh ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Ooh. ooh ♪
♪♪♪
[brakes screeching]
♪ Tense music ♪
♪♪♪
-[tires squealing]
-[Lynae] No! No!
Please.
Breathe. breathe. breathe.
[screaming]
Breathe. breathe.
breathe. breathe. breathe.
[screaming]
♪♪♪
♪ Donnie Hathaway's
"Someday We'll All Be Free" ♪
♪♪♪
[Emmett] Life is about choices.
Some choices
make our lives better...
while others come back
to haunt us.
♪ As it spins around ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Just don't let ♪
♪ The spin get you down ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Things are moving fast ♪
[Emmett] We don't always make
the right decisions.
but the hope is.
we can learn from our mistakes.
♪ Keep your self-respect ♪
♪ Your manly pride ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Get yourself ♪
♪ In gear ♪
♪ Keep your stride ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Never mind your fears ♪
♪ Brighter days
will soon be here ♪
♪ Take it from me ♪
♪ Someday ♪
♪ We'll all be free ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
[Emmett] No one knows
what the future holds.
and the past is already gone.
♪♪♪
All we can do is be grateful
for our present.
no matter what it looks like.
♪♪♪
♪ Keep on ♪
♪ Walking tall ♪
♪ Hold your head up high ♪
♪ Lay your dreams
♪ Right up ♪
♪ To the sky ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Sing your great song ♪
♪ And you'll keep going ♪
♪ Going on... ♪
[Emmett] Because even
when it seems like things
are coming to an end.
it's really just
a new beginning.
♪ We'll all be free ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Hey. just wait and see ♪
♪ Someday we'll all be free ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Take it from me ♪
♪ Someday we'll all be free ♪
♪♪♪
♪ And it won't be long ♪
♪ Take it from me ♪
♪ Someday we'll all be free ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Take it from me ♪
♪ Take it from me. take it ♪
♪ Chance the Rapper's
"No More Old Men" ♪
♪♪♪
♪ They say Chi
don't dance no more ♪
♪ And the little kids
don't got a chance no more ♪
♪ Clippers buzzin'.
cryin' grandbaby boy cousin ♪
♪ The first cut. lil man.
quit all that fussin' ♪
♪ God the Father may love you.
the world doesn't ♪
♪ That's how I learned
to put my dukes up ♪
♪ And play the dozens ♪
♪ Lessons and the strategies
of love and war ♪
♪ Chessboards
and King magazines galore ♪
♪ It's a lot less love
than it was before ♪
♪ It's a lot less old men
♪ I say we gonna live
till our hair turn white ♪
-♪ Till our hair turn white.
-♪ No law can find our names ♪
♪ No law can find our names ♪
♪ And when we run.
no one's chasin' us ♪
-♪ Chasin' us.
-♪ Streetlights on ♪
♪ The kids all come back home ♪
♪ On and on and on
and on and on ♪
♪ And on and on and on
-♪ On and on and on and on.
-♪ I know it go ♪
♪ Kids always come home ♪
♪ I said. we gonna live
till our hair turn white ♪
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm